Woman's Club of Albany; Records mss139
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Financials, 1910-2009; 2; 7.17 cubic ft.
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1924-1925 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 49)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1924-1925 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 50)
  - Literature Department Expenses, 1924-1925 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 51)
  - Albany Chamber of Commerce Dues, 1924-1931 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 52)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1925 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 53)
  - Hospitality Committee and Misc. Expenses, 1925-1926 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 54)
  - Cash Book, 1925-1938 (Oversized 3)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1926 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 55)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1926 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1926-1927 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - Public Health and Public Education Committees Expenses, 1926-1927 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1926-1927 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Fine Arts Department Expenses, 1926-1928 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - Ledger, 1926-1936 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1927 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1927-1928 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - Municipal Welfare Department, Public Health and Public Education Committees Expenses, 1927-1928 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Deforestation Section Expenses, 1927-1928 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1927-1929 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - Rentals, 1927-1938 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Literature Department Expenses, 1927-1929; 1931 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Social and Industrial Department Expenses, 1927; 1929-1930 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - Civic Section, Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1927; 1934; Undated (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1928 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1929 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - Business Meetings and Club Day Expenses and Various Receipts, 1930 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Conservation Department Expenses, 1930 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1930 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1930-1931 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - Public Education Department Expenses, 1930-1931 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - House Committee Expenses, 1930-1931; 1936-1937; Undated (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - Bank Statements, 1930-1932; 1934 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1930-1939 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1931 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - Hospitality Committee Expenses, 1931 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Language Department Expenses, 1931 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - Business Meetings and Club Day Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - Conservation Department Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - Dramatic Department and Music Department Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1931-1933 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1932 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1932-1933 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - Art Department Expenses, 1932-1934; 1940; Undated (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1933 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 37)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1933-1935 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 38)
  - Social Committee Expenses and Receipts, 1933-1934 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 39)
  - Conservation Department Expenses, 1933-1934 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 40)
  - Dramatic Department Expenses, 1933-1934; 1936; 1939 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 41)
  - Music Department Expenses, 1933-1934 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 42)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1933-1936; Undated (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 43)
  - Hospitality Committee Expenses, 1933-1934; 1937 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 44)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1934 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 45)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1935 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 46)
  - Bank Statements, 1935-1939 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 47)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1936 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 48)
  - Ledger, 1936-1943 (Box 3 (2-Financials), Folder 49)
  - Altruistic Committee Ledger, 1936-1946 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1937 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1938 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Cash Book, 1938-1947 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1939 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - American Home Department Expenses, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Language and Literature Department Expenses, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1940 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Social Committee Expenses for Business Meetings, 1940 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - Bank Statements, 1940-1943 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments (1 of 2), 1940-1946 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments (2 of 2), 1940-1946 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1941 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1942 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - Ledger, 1943-1950 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - Cash Book, 1946-1947 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - Sales Accounts, 1946-1947 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Bank Statements, 1946-1949 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - Rentals, 1946-1949 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Day Book/Cash Book, 1947-1960 (Oversized 3)
  - Completed Forms on Behalf of Employees, 1948; 1972 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1949 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - Rentals, 1949-1950 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1950 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - Ledger, 1950-1957 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - Bank Statements, 1950; 1952-1955 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1951 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Youth Co-Operation Department Card Party Expenses, 1951 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1951-1964 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1952 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - Bazaar Card Party Expenses, 1953 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - Garden Department Flower Show Expenses, 1953 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1953 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1954 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1955 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - Report on Safety Deposit Box, 1955 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Ledger, 1956-1960 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 37)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1958 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 38)
  - Messenger Expenses, 1959; 1964; 1972-1973; Undated (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 39)
  - Ledger, 1960-1962 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 40)
  - Cash Book, 1961-1975 (Oversized 3)
  - Federal Tax Returns and IRS Correspondence, 1961-1966; 1972-1973; 1994-2009 (Box 4 (2-Financials), Folder 41)
  - Membership Dues Ledger, 1962-1998 (Oversized 4)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1964 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Rentals, 1964-1965 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - NYS Women's Legislative Form Dues, 1964-1971; Undated (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Tax Exemption Forms (1 of 2), 1964-2008 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Tax Exemption Forms (2 of 2), 1964-2008 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1965 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements, 1965-1969 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1965-1976 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1966-1976; 1996; Undated (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1967 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1968 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1970 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - Lease on the Woman's Club Property, 1970-1971; 1995 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - Bank Statements, 1970-1974 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1971 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1972 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1973 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - Financial Ledger, 1973-1990 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1974 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1975 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - Bank Statements, 1975-1978 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - Church Receipts, 1975-1978; Undated (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1976 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - Account Book, 1976-1982 (Oversized 4)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1977 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Resolution by Board for Bank and Banking Responsibilities, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - Bank Statements, 1978-1982 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1979 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1980 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - Completed Grant Applications, 1980-1981; 1991-1992 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1980-1994 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1981 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1982 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1983 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements, 1983-1989 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1984 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1985 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1986 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1987 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1988 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1989 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1990 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Bank Statements, 1990-1995 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Cash Book, 1990-1996 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1991 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1992 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1993 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1994 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Legal Advice, 1994-1996 (Box 5 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1995 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1995-2005 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1996 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - Bank Statements, 1996-1999 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - Cash Book, 1996-2000 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - Card Party Expenses, 1997 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1997 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1998 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Bank Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1999 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2000 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - Bank Statements, 2000-2005 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2001 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2004 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2005 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - Financial Statements, 2007 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, Undated (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Member Expenses Book, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Music Section Expenses, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - Sales Book, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Social Committee Expenses, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
- Departments and Committees, 1911-2009; 3; 1.21 cubic ft.
  This series contains the annual reports of different departments and committees. The reports give news about each department or committee from the year, and their respective future plans. Most reports are typed, but some of the original handwritten reports sent to the Board secretary are included as well. In addition, there are meeting minutes from select committees.
  - Dramatic Department, 1911-1915; Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 1)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Minutes, 1912-1918 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 2)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Book, 1913-1918 (Oversized 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1919 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 3)
  - Department and Committees Directory, Lists of Duties and Committee Rules, 1919-1946; Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1920-1921 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1921-1922 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1922-1923 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 7)
  - Travelers' Aid Committee, 1922-1924; Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 8)
  - Original Annual Committee Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 9)
  - Typewritten Annual Committee Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 10)
  - A Program of Community Study, Possibly Used by Municipal Welfare Department, 1924 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (1 of 2), 1924-1925 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (2 of 2), 1924-1925 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (1 of 2), 1925-1928 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (2 of 2), 1925-1928 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 15)
  - Garden Section Yearbook, 1927-1928 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 16)
  - Annual Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1928-1934 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 17)
  - Annual Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1928-1934 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 18)
  - Secretary Report and Garden Section Reports, 1931-1942 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 19)
  - Annual Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1934-1938 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 20)
  - Annual Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1934-1938 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 21)
  - Committee Directories, 1935-1941 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 22)
  - Altruistic Committee, 1937-1941 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 23)
  - Annual Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1938-1943 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 24)
  - Annual Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1938-1943 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 25)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1944-1951 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 26)
  - Garden Department, 1950-1951; 1957; 1962 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 27)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1952 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1957-1958 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 30)
  - Annual Department Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 31)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 32)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 33)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 34)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 35)
  - Annual Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 36)
  - Annual Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 37)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 38)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 39)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 40)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 41)
  - Garden Department, 1970-1973 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 42)
  - Department Reports, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 43)
  - Committee Lists, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 44)
  - Annual Reports, 2009 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 45)
  - Building Committee Meeting Agenda, 2009 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 46)
  - Building Committee Report, 2009 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 47)
  - Communications Committee Report, 2009 (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 48)
  - Housing Committee Rules, Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 49)
  - Annual Department Reports, Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 50)
  - Garden Section Annual Report and Member List, Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 51)
  - International Affairs Annual Report, Undated (Box 1 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 52)
- Membership, 1910-2009; 4; 2.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically within subseries 1, 2, 4 and 5.
  Arranged chronologically within subseries 3.
  This series is comprised of five subseries and documents various aspects of Womans Club of Albany membership. There are applications for new members which range from 1938-2004. At first the applications were kept by themselves in stacks by year. Then, starting in 1968, the WCA began attaching a copy the Clubs acceptance letter to the new member application. The last few sets of dates (1994, 1996, 2001, and 2004) revert back to the original filing format; without an acceptance letter attached. These membership applications and acceptance letters are filed chronologically.
  The WCA also kept resignation records. It did this in various ways, including index cards and resignation letters. The index cards begin as handwritten cards and transition to typed cards. Amongst the resignations are index cards of members dropped because of unpaid dues. These index cards are grouped into three different categories to maintain original order. Beginning in the 1960s, the WCA started keeping track of resignation letters and letters from the WCA acknowledging the member's resignation. The WCA also kept records of member deaths.
  As with Series 7, Publications, the Womans Club of Albany often changed the layout of the information it published. Every year, the Club produced a new membership list. From 1917-1929, the WCA published membership lists as booklets. In 1933 the WCA switched and began publishing membership lists as pamphlets. As the WCA also switched to monthly news pamphlets around this time, it suggests the WCA mailed out a new membership list, with the monthly news, and the Officers, Departments, and Committees Directory pamphlet once every year. From 1968-1971 the Club published a combination of the Officers Directory and membership in a small booklet.
  Please note that from 1911-1942 the Womans Club of Albany would typically make the Governor of New Yorks wife an honorary member. This included Eleanor Roosevelt during Franklin Delano Roosevelt's tenure as governor. It is unknown when and why this tradition stopped.
  - Early Member Index Cards, 1910-1931; 4.1
    - Index cards, A-Y, 1910-1931, Undated (Card-file 1)
  - Early Membership Applications and Resignations, 1917-1927; 4.2
    - Early Membership Applications A, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 1)
    - Early Membership Applications B, 1917-1924 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 2)
    - Early Membership Applications C, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 3)
    - Early Membership Applications D, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 4)
    - Early Membership Applications E, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 5)
    - Early Membership Applications F, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 6)
    - Early Membership Applications G, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 7)
    - Early Membership Applications H, I, &J, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 8)
    - Early Membership Applications K &L, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 9)
    - Early Membership Applications M, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 10)
    - Early Membership Applications N &O, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 11)
    - Early Membership Applications P &Q, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 12)
    - Early Membership Applications R, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 13)
    - Early Membership Applications S, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 14)
    - Early Membership Applications T, U, &V, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 15)
    - Early Membership Applications W, 1917-1925 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 16)
    - Early Membership Applications Z, 1917-1923 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 17)
    - Early Resignations, A, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 18)
    - Early Resignations, B, 1915-1923; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 19)
    - Early Resignations, C, 1915-1923; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 20)
    - Early Resignations, D, 1912-1921; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 21)
    - Early Resignations, E &F, 1911-1924; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 22)
    - Early Resignations, G, 1912-1922; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 23)
    - Early Resignations, H, I, &J, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 24)
    - Early Resignations, K &L, 1912-1924; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 25)
    - Early Resignations, M, 1911-1924; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 26)
    - Early Resignations, N &O, 1916-1922; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 27)
    - Early Resignations, P, 1915-1922; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 28)
    - Early Resignations, R, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 29)
    - Early Resignations, S, 1911-1920; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 30)
    - Early Resignations, T, U, &V, 1915-1922; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 31)
    - Early Resignations, W &Y, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 32)
    - Early Resignations, A, 1924-1927 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 33)
    - Early Resignations, B, 1924-1927 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 34)
    - Early Resignations, C, 1924-1927 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 35)
    - Early Resignations, D, 1924-1927 (Box 3 (4-Membership), Folder 36)